Your Majesty.
Greetings, Sister.
Hmph.
Hmph. Your Majesty.
Didn't you say yesterday
that you wanted to try some new tricks with me?
Why are you staring blankly today?
Why are you with another sister today?
I guess I came
at a bad time.
Hmph.
Your Majesty,
where are the rest of the name tags?
What name tags? You are not allowed to flip them.
How dare she knock over the green-headed tags
to monopolize His Majesty.
This Cangyue's
good days are over.
Lady Cang,
the Emperor cannot favor you alone.
You should show equal favor to everyone.
Humph.
If I knew other sisters were coming,
I wouldn't have come today.
Your Majesty.
Haven't I already flipped the tags?
Why aren't you announcing the names?
Your Majesty, this...
Eunuch Sun,
do you want to watch too?
Oh dear,
I wouldn't dare.
Your Majesty, please enjoy yourself.
Go.
I will take my leave.
These concubines,
do you really not like any of them?
They are just a bunch of women
sent by my aunt.
Women sent by your aunt are still women.
Besides, they are so pretty.
If you win them over,
they could even help you instigate a rebellion.
Acting is acting.
What are you doing with your hands? Where are you putting them?
You don't look the part.
If I don't help you,
you'll blow your cover.
You play the role of a tyrant quite well.
However,
if you want to find an actor like yourself,
who is equally matched,
those concubines act much better than I do.
After all, I still have to rely on him to deal with the Grand Princess.
I can't piss him off.
Alright, I know.
They were all sent by the Grand Princess.
I won't taint you.
You know...
Walls have ears.
Who says my acting is bad?
Look. The fish
took the bait, didn't it?
Oh, stop looking.
These paintings are shoddy.
What's so good about them?
Come, sit down first.
Come on.
Your Majesty, they have arrived.
Cang Yue
greets Your Highness.
I will soon
select three new male concubines.
You are just in time.
Help me see which one is suitable.
Your Highness,
a constant companion
cannot be chosen from portraits.
Very well.
Ah, I am thirsty.
Your Highness, please have some tea.
You are quite tolerant.
No wonder His Majesty favors only you.
It seems that in the future,
His Majesty will have another sweet companion by his side.
I have prepared a cup of poisoned wine
and a lifetime of wealth.
Make your choice.
If you are smart,
you should know what to choose.
Cangyue thanks Your Highness for your appreciation.
I will do my utmost
and will not hesitate even if I have to die ten thousand times.
To have a new partner poison the Emperor.
Si Xinglan couldn't be that stupid.
Your Highness, as you instructed,
I watched Cangyue
put the poison into the porridge with my own eyes.
However,
I didn't see anything unusual with His Majesty.
Could it be some new trick?